Konvitz, Milton R. Papers /4039
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II: Subject FIles, 1942-1986
  - Featherbedding (Box 90, Folder 22)
    Manuscript, "Legislative Shackles on Featherbedding Practices," by William L. Brach, no date.
  - Federal Aid to Education (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Federal Aid to Education (Box 90, Folder 24)
    Memorandum from Herman Orentlicher, American Association of University Professors, regarding the Association position on current proposals for federal aid for students, particularly as embodied in the Hartke Bill (S. 2490, 88th Congress)
  - Federal Aid to Education (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - Federal Aid to Education (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    minutes, American Civil Liberties Union Board of Directors, February 15, 1965
  - Federal Aid to Education (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Federal Aid to Education (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Federal Aid to Education Bills (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Federal Aid to Education - Jewish (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Federal School Bill, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Federal Aid to Education (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Federal Courts (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Federal Income (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Federal Incorporation Act (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Federal Judicial Center (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service (FMCS) (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Federal Power (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Federal - State (Box 91, Folder 14)
    Lecture notes, Industrial and Labor Relations 300 and 600, "The New National Labor Relations Board Jurisdictional Standards"
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC) (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Federalism (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Feinberg Law (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Feinberg Law (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Feldman, Herman (Box 91, Folder 19)
    "A Survey of Research in the Field of Industrial Relations," by the Advisory Committee on Industrial Relations, Herman Feldman, Investigator
  - Fellowships (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Fern College (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Fever, Lewis S. (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Fiedler, Leslie A. (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Fifth Amendment (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Fifth Amendment (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Fighting Words (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Fighting Words - Offensive Words (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Filibuster (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Filibuster (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Financial Reporting (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Fingerprint (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - First Amendment (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - First Amendment (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - First Amendment - Articles (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Fisk University (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Flag (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Flag (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Flag Desecration (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Flag - Law and Cases (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Flag Salute (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Food Stamps (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Forced Labor, 1938-1955 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    1955 report, "Forced Labor in the 'People's Democracies'," by Free Europe Committee, Incorporated; 1938 pamphlet, "Prison Industries Reorganization Administration, Bulletin Number 1;" report, not dated, "Report on Legal and Illegal Forms of Forced Labor in the United States," by R. Watts, National Secretary of the Workers Defense League; 1951 report, "Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Slavery (Second Session)," by the United Nations Economic and Social Council.
  - Ford, Benson (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Ford Motor Company (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Ford Strike (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Aid (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Aid (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Foreign Countries (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Labor (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Labor Relations (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Languages, Affairs (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Relations (including foreign aid) (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Forest Home (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Forest Home Chapel (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Forests (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Fortas, Justice Abe (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Foundation, 1954 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    1954 letter, with attachment, signed by Senator Pat McCarran
  - Foundations, 1954-1969 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    1954 report, "Summary of Activities of Carnegie Corporation of New York, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace" to the Special Committee of the house of Representatives to Investigate Tax Exempt Foundations
  - Foundation for Economic Education (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Foundry Occupations (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Fourteenth Amendment (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Fourth Amendment (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Fox, Marvin, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    1961 reprint, "Tillich's Ontology and God" signed by Marvin Fox
  - France, 1964-1968 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Frankfurter, Mr. Justice, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    1965 letter to the editor of the New York Times on Justice Felix Frankfurter obituary
  - Franck, Isaac, 1977-1979 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    reprint, no date, of chapter 14 of "The Philosophy of Baruch Spinoza," entitled "Spinoza's Logic of Inquiry: Rationalist or Experientialist?" signed by Isaac Franck; 1977 reprint of chapter 9 of "Psychiatry and the Humanities, Volume 2," entitled "Spinoza, Freud, and Hampshire on Psychic Freedom," signed by Isaac Franck; 1979 reprint, "Was Spinoza a 'Jewish' Philosopher?" signed by Isaac Franck; 1977 reprint, "Self-Realization as Ethical Norm: A Critique," signed by Isaac Franck
  - Franks Brothers (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Fraternities (Box 93, Folder 21)
    Regarding discrimination at Cornell's fraternities
  - Fraternities (Box 93, Folder 22)
    1966 memorandum to M.R. Convicts from Steven L. Werner regarding Fraternities
  - Free Enterprise (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Free Press (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Free Press - Free Trial, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    1969 memorandum, American Civil Liberties Union working document, not for public distribution, to the Board of Directors, from the due Process Committee, regarding Fair Trial/Fair Press.
  - Free Speech (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Free Speech (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Free Speech (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Free Speech - Fighting Words (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Free Speech - Loudspeakers (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Free Speech and Press (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Free Speech - Skokie (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Freedom (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Freedom Academy (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Freedom House, 1965-1967 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    Newsletter, scattered issues 1965-1967, "News Letter" by Freedom House
  - Freedom House (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Freedom of Information (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Freedom of Speech, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    "Working Paper for Consideration by the New York Civil Liberties Union Board Submitted by the First Amendment Legal Panel," not for public distribution, by J.S. Gutman
  - Freedom of Travel (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Freedom, Outlook for (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Freedom to Read (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Freeland League, 1947-1948 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    Newsletter, scattered issues 1947-1948, "Freeland Bulletin"
  - "The Freeman", 1950-1954 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    newsletter, 1950, 1954
  - Freeman, Harrow (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Freud (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Friedman, Milton (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Fringe Benefits (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Fringe Benefits (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Fringe Issues (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Fujii Case (Fujii versus California) (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Fulbright Act, 1956 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    1956 letter, with attachments, signed by Senator J.W. Fulbright
  - Full Employment (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Fund for Education Concerning World Peace Through World Law (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Fund for the Republic, 1956 (Box 94, Folder 29)
    1956 memorandum to all grantees, from Robert M. Hutchins, Fund for the Republic, Incorporated, regarding blacklisting.
  - Gambling (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Gandhi (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Gannon, Father, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    circa 1948 "An Answer to Father Gannon," by Professor M.R. Konvitz, 3 pages.
  - General (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - General (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - General Education (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - General Electric (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - General Motors (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Geneva (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Genocide, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    1952 letter, with attachment, signed by Philip B. Perlman, Solicitor General of the United States.
  - Genocide (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - George Junior Republic (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - German Trade Union Movement, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    1949 reprint, "Communists in German Labor Organizations," signed by Matthew A. Kelly
  - Germany (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Ghana (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Ghent, Donald F. (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Gifts (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Goethe (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Goldberg, Arthur J. (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Goldwater, Barry (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Gompers, Samuel (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Good Samaritan (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Goodman, Paul (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Gotesky, Rubin (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Gotesky, Rubin, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    1966 reprint, "The Lecture and Critical Thinking," signed by Rubin Gotesky; "A Proposal for an Experiment in Testing Religious Claims to Produce Altruistic Persons," for private circulation only, by Rubin Gotesky, no date.
  - Government Agencies, United States (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Government Employees (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Government Employees (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Government Employees - Condon-Wadlin (Box 95, Folder 29)
    Handwritten notes regarding New York city Policemen, Yonkers Garbage Strike
  - Government Employees - General (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Government Employees - Policemen, Firemen (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Government Employees - Teachers (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Government Employees - Transit (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Government - General (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Graft (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Graham, Howard Jay (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Grand Jury (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Great Books (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Great Britain (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Greece (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Greek and Roman (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Green, William (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Greening of America (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Grievance Procedure (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Grievances (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Griffin Case, 1957 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    1957 reprint, "The Griffin Case - Poverty and the Fourteenth Amendment" signed by Bertram F. Wilcox
  - Griswold, Erwin (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Grossing's (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Group Defamation (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Group Hospital Service (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Group Libel (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Group Libel (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Group Libel, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    1950 reprint, "Group Libel" signed by Joseph Tanenhaus
  - Guam (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Guaranteed Annual Wage (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Guggenheim, John Simon (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Guidance (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Guilt by Association (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Guilty Pleas (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Guinea (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - Gun Control (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Gun Control, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 30)
    1981 memorandum to the Board of Directors from the Due Process Committee, American Civil Liberties Union, regarding gun control
  - Guns (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Guttmacher Institute (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - Habeas, Ralph (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - Habeas Corpus (Box 96, Folder 34)
  - Habeas Corpus (Box 96, Folder 35)
  - Habeas Corpus (Box 96, Folder 36)
  - Haber, William, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 37)
    1968 reprint, "Authority Without Freedom," signed by William Haber
  - Hacker, Louis M. (Box 96, Folder 38)
  - Haifa, University of (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - "Hair" (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - "Hair", 1975 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Haiti (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Haitian "Boat People" (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Hall, Jerome (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Handbills (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Handicapped, 1949 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    1949 news release, United States Department of Labor
  - Handicapped (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Handicapped, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    1976 newsletter, "NCLA Newsletter" by the National Center for Law and the Deaf
  - Handicapped, 1977-1978 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    1977. 1978 memorandum to the Board of Directors from the Equality Committee, American Civil Liberties Union, regarding the rights of the physically disabled.
  - Hanslowe, Kurt (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Happiness (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Happiness (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Happiness (Box 97, Folder 14)
    Handwritten notes
  - Harlan, John Marshall (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Harvard (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Harvard (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Harvard-Brandeis Cooperative Research on Israel's Legal Development, 1956 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    1956 report, "Draft Family Code for the State of Israel"
  - Harvard-Brandeis Cooperative Research on Israel's Legal Development, 1953-1954 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    1953 report, "An Evidence Bill for Israel;" report, not dated, "Law of Evidence" (Ministry Bill); 1954 report, "A Succession Bill for Israel)
  - Harvard Law School - Israel Cooperative Research, 1952 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    Minutes, 1952, New York Conference on the Israeli Succession Bill on 1952; 1952 report, "A Succession Bill for Israel"
  - Hatch Act (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Hatch Act (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Hate Literature (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Hawaii Strike (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Hawk, David (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Hawkins and Shaw (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Haynesworth (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Hays, Arthur Garfield, 1963-1964 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    1963-1964 reports, "Annual Report of Arthur Garfield Hays Civil Liberties Program"
  - H-Bomb (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Health (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Health and Welfare Funds (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Health Insurance (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Health Programs (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Hearsay (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Hebrew (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Hebrew Culture Foundation (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Hebrew Teachers College (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Hebrew Union College (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Hebrew University (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Helsinki, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 21)
    1977. 1978 memorandum to CRC's (Communication Resource Center's) Governing Council, Lawyer's Committee, from Phil Baum, Director of the Commission on International Affairs, American Jewish Congress, regarding the Scharansky Case - the legal setting.
  - Helsinki, 1981-1982 (Box 98, Folder 22)
    Remarks, Speeches, and Statements given by Ambassador Max M. Kampelman, Chairman, United States Delegation, Plenary Session, Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe (CSCE)
  - Helsinki (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Helsinki (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Herzberg, Will (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Heresy (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Heritage Foundation (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - Higher Education (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - Higher Education Act, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Highlander Folk School (Box 98, Folder 30)
  - Highways (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - Hillel, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    "Minutes of the Meeting of the National Hillel Faculty Consultative Committee" (first), 1963, of which Konvitz was a participant.
  - Hillman, Sidney (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Hippies and Teeny Boppers (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Hiring Hall, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    1966 report, "Annual Report to the Board of Trustees of the American Histadrut Cultural Exchange Institute," of which M.R. Konvitz was a member of the Joint Curriculum Committee; handwritten lecture notes
  - Hiring Hall (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Hiss, Alger (Box 99, Folder 6)
    "How Not to Fight Communism" by M.R. Konvitz, no date
  - Hiss Trial (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Histadrut, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    1976-
  - Histadrut (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Histadrut (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Histadrut (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - "Historic Ithaca and Tomkins County, New York" (newsletter), 1978-1981 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Historicism (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Historical Cases (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - History (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Hobart and William Smith Colleges (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Hoffa, James R. (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Hoffman, Paul G. (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Holiday Practices (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Hollander, Louis (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Holmes, 1964 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    1964 reprint, "The Judge as Spectator" signed by Yosal Rogat
  - Holocaust (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Holocaust (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - "The Home Front" (newsletter) - published by the American Jewish Committee, 1946 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Homosexuals (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Homosexuals, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    Minutes, American Civil Liberties Union, Board of Directors
  - Homosexuals (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Homosexuals (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Honesty (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Honors (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Honor System (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    1960 reprint, "Pragmatism and the Tragic Sense of Life," signed by Sidney Hook
  - Hook, Sidney, 1946 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    1946 reprint, "Synthesis or Eclecticism?" signed by Sidney hook
  - Hospitals (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Hot Cargo (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Hot Cargo (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Hotel (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Hours of Work (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    1966 newsletter by the National Committee to Abolish the House Un- American Activities Committee
  - House Un-American Activities Committee (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Housing, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    1965 letter, with attachment, signed by Representative Donald M. Fraser
  - Housing, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    1966 report, "Neighborhood Stabilization: A Program," special report by Southern Regional Council
  - Housing (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Housing (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Housing, 1951 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    1951 confidential report, "American Jewish Congress and Discrimination in Housing," by the American Jewish Congress
  - Housing (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Housing (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Housing (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Housing (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Housing (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Housing - General (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Housing - General (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Housing - Poverty and Housing the Poor (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Housing - Public and Exclusionary Zoning Laws (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Housing: Public - "Forest Hills' Controversy" (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Housing: Public - "NDCH/Trends in Housing" (Box 102, Folder 11)
    NDCH?
  - Housing: Public - "Publications on Equal Opportunity" (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Housing: Public - Racial Integration (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Housing: Public - Tenants' Rights and Organizations (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Housing, Races (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Housing: Racial Discrimination (Private Ownership) (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Howard University (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Human Relations (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Human Resources (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Human Rights (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Human Rights - International, 1976-1978 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    Newsletter, scattered issues 1976-1978, "Human Rights Bulletin," by the International League for Human Rights
  - Human Rights - International (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Human Rights - International, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    1954 letter, with attachments, signed by Walter Kotschnig, Director, Office of United Nations Economic and Social Affairs
  - Human Rights Day (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Humanist (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Humanities (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Humanities (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Humor (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Humphrey, Hubert (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Hunger (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Hunger (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Hunger (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Hunger (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Hunger (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Hunger (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Hunger (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Hutchins, Robert M. (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Hutchinson, Anne (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Hypnosis (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU) (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Ehud (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Illegitimacy (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Illegitimacy (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Illiteracy (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - International Labor Organization (ILO) (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Immigration (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Immigration (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Immigration, 1949-1965 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    1949 reprint, "The Race Question in American Immigration Statistics," signed by Hans Zeisel; copies of a 1965 letter, with attachment, by David Carliner regarding his statement before the Immigration Subcommittee on behalf of the American Civil Liberties Union.
  - Immigration, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    1964 form letter from the Sherman Defense Committee
  - Immigration, 1955-1957 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    1955 newsletter, "New York Beacon," by the New York Committee for the Protection of Foreign Born; 1957 reprint, signed by Harry N. Rosenfield, "Historical Research as a Tool for Immigration Policy"
  - Immigration, 1953 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    1953 joint memorandum, American Jewish Committee and Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, to Community Relations Committee, American Jewish Committee Area Offices and Anti-Defamation League Regional Offices, From: Sidney Liskofsky and Sol Rabkin, regarding the Refugee Relief Act of 1953
  - Immigration Act, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Immigration - McCarren Act, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    Handwritten notes, 1950, and typewritten draft of "Substantive Constitutional Rights," "Procedural Due Process," "The Plenary Power to Exclude," "Due Process of Law in Immigration Policy," and footnotes.
  - Immunity (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - Immunity (Box 105, Folder 1)
    1954 paper, "The Courage to be Oneself" signed by Jerome Nathanson
  - Immunity (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Immunity (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Impeachment, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    1974 news release regarding American Civil Liberties Union campaign to impeach President Nixon
  - Impeachment (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Impound Funds (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Imprisonment (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Incentive Plans (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Income (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Incomes (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Income Tax (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Indecent Exposure (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Independent Contractor (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Independent Contractor (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Independent Zionists of America (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - India (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - India (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - India (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Indian Affairs (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Indians, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    1966 reprint, "The Negro and the Indian: A Comparison of their Constitution Rights" signed by Albert E. Kane
  - Indians (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Indians, 1950 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    1950 letter, with attachment, signed by Reva Beck Bosone, member of Congress from Utah
  - Indians (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Indians (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Indians (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Indians, American (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Indians and Indian Affairs (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Indictment (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Indigent Defendants (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Individual, The (Box 106, Folder 9)
    Handwritten Notes
  - Individualism (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Indonesia (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Inducing Breach of Contract (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Industrial Accident Prevention (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - "Industrial Information Bulletin", 1948 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    February 1948, by Commonwealth of Australia, Department of Labour and National Service
  - "Industrial Psychology and Personnel Practice", 1947-1948 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    Scattered issues, 1947 and 1948, by the Commonwealth of Australia, Department of Labour and National Service